Gen Z. [music] A new report shows that
generation is leaning on their parents
for more financial help.
>> Can we actually make broad ownership a
reality? A future with relatively few
owners is inherently fragile. We're
building a financial super app.
>> Are you setting [music] them up in a
situation where the odds are are stacked
against them to [music] actually make
money?
>> A lot of people criticize us because
they think we incentivize active trading
and prediction markets. [music] That's
when you can kind of get into trouble.
>> Get this. The richest 1% controls more
wealth now than at any time in more than
a half century.
>> Alarm bells have started ringing.
There's a small [music] circle of
wealthy insiders that's benefiting from
all the growth.
>> How much has AI changed the game?
>> Humans overseeing agents, seeing how
many you can [music] actually employ,
including when you're sleeping.
>> So, do you think though with Robin Hood
eventually you could have just a few
people running [music] the entire
company? Um,
it's
>> that's just dangling the carrot, huh?
[laughter]
>> Vlad from Robin Hood. Thank you so much
for coming on the iced coffee hour.
>> Great to see you guys again.
>> Last time you sat here, you still drove
a used car. Since then, your app Robin
Hood has grown 125 billion with a B in
assets under custody, which is 50% in
one year. Today, Robin Hood stock is up
3%. Which some people are like, "Oh, 3%
whatever, whatever, whatever." Maybe I'm
up $3,000. You're up $150 million or
whatever just in one day. I have to
know, are you still driving a used car?
>> I can afford a new car now. No. Uh yeah.
Uh I had a used 911 Turbo S last year.
It was kind of a a holdover because I
had uh ordered a new GT3 which is a a
very fun car and uh and so now I drive
that. So I have a GT3 Touring manual
transmission. The thing cooks.
>> Do you have a long commute?
>> No, not too long. I mean much shorter
now that I got this new [laughter] car.
Uh yeah, anywhere from uh 10 minutes to
20 minutes depending on traffic. Now,
when you walk into Porsche, do they just
give you any car that you want, or do
you have to kind of play the game a
little bit to work your way up?
>> A lot of brands
uh reward loyalty. So, if you're loyal
to a particular car uh maker or a
dealership, uh they they take care of
you. And not a lot of them just uh I
mean, some some do this differently, but
I think for a lot of them, they do
actually value loyal customers. uh
relative to just a random famous person
reaching out to them who who wants
something. So to answer your question, I
don't think it has helped me very much.
I kind of had to wait over a year just
like everyone else.
>> So as the CEO and founder of Robin Hood,
if not the stock price, what is the
metric that you obsess over every day?
>> I don't think there's one metric really
because I mean Robin Hood works on many
things. We have lots of businesses.
Increasingly, my job is kind of I I have
folks that effectively function as CEOs
of their businesses reporting to me. And
if I had to think about
what idea or
what concept is associated most with
Robin Hood, what we can own, it's really
ownership. This idea of
a world or a future with relatively few
owners is inherently fragile and can we
actually
make broad ownership a reality. Can we
make it so that you know more people own
uh equities and and also all the other
assets around us. So one thing that I
have been talking about recently is
percentage of households in America that
own equities. So right now that's
something like 65%. Before Robin Hood
came along it was in the low 50s. So I
think we meaningfully contributed and
now the question is can we get to 95%
plus which I think with initiatives like
the Trump accounts with our work on
private markets it makes that
increasingly likely and can we also
force the rest of the world to catch up
which is where things like tokenization
come in. Can we actually make it so that
it's really easy for the best stocks and
and other real world assets from the US
to be distributed globally so that
everyone can kind of benefit from all
the great work we're doing here?
>> Now, how much of that though is an
ownership problem, an education problem,
or just a most people don't have enough
money problem?
>> Yeah, that's a problem too. most people
don't have enough money and I think
that's where forced uh ownership or
default ownership has been really
impactful. Like one of the things that
really moved the needle in the US was
the employer sponsored 401k where if you
have an employer uh and they have a 401k
program effectively it's like free money
to participate and get the the employer
salary match and and that by itself
moved ownership by tens of percentage
points and now you see countries all
over the world trying to replicate this
Trump accounts as ownership by default
too. Every single child born in this
country gets $1,000 funded by Treasury.
And then now you're seeing
philanthropists like Michael Dell, Ray
Dallio sponsoring their states. Michael
Dell obviously is a much bigger
sponsorship where he targets lower
income zip codes all over the country.
The solution to a lot of people not
having enough money is um making it by
default and having sort of like these
employer and government sponsored
programs coupled with with philanthropy
to uh help the ones that are kind of
living paycheck to paycheck or have less
means to uh own stocks as well.
>> So in order to grow $125 billion in
assets under custody in one year, I mean
that's just honestly unfeasible. Like I
I can't even imagine that that is
congratulations on the success. I'm
curious. You can't just say okay well
we're going to grow in assets under
custody. Like there's and then grow like
there are certain things that you have
to do in order for that to ensue. And so
I'm curious what are the things that
like the main things you focused on that
have made that big of an impact on your
company.
>> Well, we we have sort of three
ways that we're furthering ownership and
and really what assets under custody is
is a measure of how well we're
succeeding. If more assets are on the
platform, then that's more things that
people are owning. The first thing is
serving our active traders. Active
traders still very much the core of the
business. A lot of the asset growth is
just people bringing in money so that
they can trade different things. So if
we make uh the the assets that we offer
great and if if we have a great options
trading experience, great equities
trading, we've added futures more
recently and prediction markets as well.
People will bring in money to trade and
they're they'll tell their friends about
it as well. So we've seen a lot of
growth there. And you know, you can you
can also look at our market share across
all of the core assets, the volumes. uh
we hit lots of records in Q2 which we
just reported on you know record and
equities trading that that's really the
engine right equities is our core
business what we started with and you
know last quarter people were trading
more equities in Robin Hood uh than back
in 2021 when we saw GameStop which was
also like a crazy high period right so
organically through compounding of our
business we've exceeded that sort of
like peak uh options trading all-time
high. We're now the top options trading
platform uh in terms of retail market
share. So, we've surpassed all of the
incumbents who keep just combining with
each other. So, the the task at hand
gets harder, but but we've we've crossed
over into number one in options. And
then futures and prediction markets have
been super high as well. So, I'd say
that that's one bucket. The second
bucket is just um how can we be your
financial home for life? So it's this
idea of lifelong ownership. Can we get
someone from when they're born to
teenage years to college, first job, uh
when they have kids, can we help them
with all their financial needs as well
all the way through to like a
inheritance event. So we've been
building things to fill out that entire
life cycle. Trump accounts and custodial
being a great example, but also recently
we've added trust accounts which make it
really easy to if you have a trust
onboard into Robin Hood. We've got joint
accounts, so if you have a spouse or
partner, you can bring them into Robin
Hood as well. And and Robin Hood banking
has been huge there. That's been scaling
really really rapidly. Billions of
assets, really high direct deposit
attach rate. And that's really about can
we get someone to put in their paycheck
into Robin Hood? And that allows us to
help them do things like how much of
your money should go into retirement,
how much should go into your
self-directed taxable brokerage account,
how much should go into strategies. So,
it's kind of been putting together all
the pieces so that we can actually serve
all of your financial needs and that if
they're at Robin Hood, you you benefit
rather than having them dispersed among
lots of other banks and kind of siloed.
>> How much of that is just the deposit
bonus where I see crazy bonuses like 3%
on crypto, 1% for retirement accounts? I
I think I've even seen one and a half
percent on something.
>> The deposit bonuses help, but it's it's
a minority of it. I mean I think we we
share we share numbers on you know what
percentage of AATS for instance come in
via deposit incentives versus otherwise
and you know it's it's a good chunk of
of AATS activity but still AATS is kind
of a minority of of the overall money
moving in and out of the the platform.
>> Congrats on launching the AI investing.
As soon as I saw you guys launch that I
was looking over Twitter or X and I saw
it everywhere. Everyone was talking
about it all over Reddit. Congrats on
that. That I felt like was a huge leap
forward in terms of what brokerages are
able and willing to do. I'm curious, how
does a deal like that actually come to
fruition and with AI investing agents?
Are people actually making money?
>> Yeah. Um, so we uh we don't really have
a partnership per se. Um, basically I
think what you're referring to is we
launched two things, a Gentic trading
and a Gentic card. And what that allows
people to do is if you have your your
Clawed Code or your codeex or your other
AI agent, you can access the Robin Hood
tools. And the idea is anything that you
can do on your phone with Robin Hood,
you should be able to have your AI agent
do through kind of the paved path of the
MCP server. So, we launched with
equities trading. And since then, we've
expanded into options. We've we've
announced crypto, so that's coming soon.
And we keep adding little tools here and
there, like recently, we rolled out the
ability to see your tax lots. So for
those that uh can use AI agents and are
reasonably sophisticated, it gives you
kind of the the power of Robin Hood at
your disposal.
>> And what data are you seeing with people
that are using AI agents to invest? Like
are they are they making money? Are they
losing money? How like how does that
work out with with broad data?
>> I don't really look too closely at their
returns. Um but we we're getting a lot
of people trying it out. Uh we've had
over 100,000 people actually create a
Gentic accounts and and they're driving
decent volume and they're doing really
sophisticated things like you know
they're they're uh pulling together all
kinds of data sources from all over the
internet and kind of combining it into
strategies. I I'd say um my background
is from algorithmic trading. So before I
started Robin Hood, I would write
trading strategies and it was an
incredibly challenging thing because
you'd have to be a programmer. You'd
have to worry about all sorts of things
and you needed um really deep
integrations with legacy financial
companies to even get access to the
markets because back then you couldn't
trade through a normal broker. they were
charging you $10 every trade. So, I
think what's happening is it's making
that power, the the ability to trade
algorithmically much more democratized,
but there's still challenges. For
example, sometimes these agents
themselves aren't optimized for trading.
They'll tell you, "I don't want to trade
right now. I don't think this is a good
idea." And then you really have to work
hard to make sure it does the thing you
want to do. Well, what if it's trying to
save the person from losing money and it
just sees something, it's like, "Hey,
this is a bad trade."
>> Most of the time when they don't uh
trade, it's not actually for that
reason. I think it's just
>> doesn't want to. It just feel doesn't
feel like it.
>> Yeah. It just doesn't feel like it.
>> Didn't have coffee that morning.
>> Yeah. It's like, h, you know, I
recommend that you actually open up your
Robin Hood app and and and put the trade
in that way. Yeah. Because I I don't
think that
trading activity is in the training
data. like you don't have like aentic
trading traces like you would
programming traces. So this is just a
new thing that hasn't been done before.
>> Given the way things are going though,
do you think eventually financial
advisers are going to be obsolete? And
really quick, I just got to say that if
you're running your business out of your
personal bank account, you are one bad
client away from a real problem. We're
talking your personal savings, your
home, everything you own is on the line.
That of course is why we're partnered
with Northwest Registered Agent. For $39
a month plus state fees, they form your
LLC and make sure you're actually
protected. You get your state filing,
operating agreement, membership
certificates, and banking resolutions.
All the paperwork that makes it
official.
>> Once you're an LLC, your personal assets
are generally kept separate from
whatever happens in the business. Plus,
with Northwest's free identity services,
you get a domain, website, email, phone
line, brand protection, and mail
forwarding, all included, so your
business looks like a real company from
day one.
>> And Northwest uses their own address in
your filings instead of yours, so your
home address never goes in public
record. If you've been running your
business out of your personal accounts
for too long, it is finally time to fix
it. Just go to
northwestregisteredagent.com/ic
today to get started. That's
northwestregistered agent.com/ic
or click the link down below in the
description to get your LLC filed.
>> Thank you so much to Northwest
Registered agent for sponsoring this
episode. Given the way things are going
though, do you think eventually
financial adviserss are going to be
obsolete?
>> Um, I think there's always going to be
some need for humans. Um, like a
financial advisor
provides very different services. It's
kind of like a consigary to you, right?
And it's someone that is responsible and
can help you
um make life decisions. A lot a lot of
people have financial adviserss and
they're like um almost a member of the
family. I think in that sense
some people will always want a human. I
don't know if that type of like close
emotional relationship is going to be
replaced by AI. I think right now people
are using AI to
sanity check um certain things and you
know they say okay is my adviser are
they telling me something that makes
sense but um there's like a human need
that makes it really really hard uh to
trust machines for everything because at
the end of the day you want someone to
be responsible and and I think it's it's
hard to have the AI AI take
responsibility. In fact, you know, if if
you can own something, if you're a
fiduciary, it's it's a different bar.
So,
>> yeah, but even if someone is held
responsible for something, it doesn't
necessarily fix the actual problem if
they make a mistake. Like, I've had
mistakes made before for myself. And
it's like, yeah, they might make a
problem, but then actually correcting
that problem is more work than just
dealing with the problem.
>> Yeah. I mean at a certain level you're
always responsible for
>> your own financial decisions even if
it's like hey I've hired if if it's an
adviser I've hired this adviser I choose
to keep working with them so it's it's
my responsibility as well
>> I think still a lot of people just don't
want to think about it you um
>> you know you come across a lot of people
and a lot of a lot of them have made
money and they say I just want to spend
very little of my time thinking about
finances and
they're not they're probably not going
to prompt a claw agent or or open AAI.
They just want a a person that takes
that entirely off their plate. I think
the more likely scenario is is you'll
see fee compression in that industry.
>> You'll see fee compression um because
basically for a while there have been
two models. There's been kind of robo
advisory, which is asset management, but
you don't actually have at your disposal
the full comprehensive estate planning,
financial planning, tax planning. It's
just very siloed toward um financial
advice and investment management. And
then you have fullervice financial
adviserss that kind of take over.
They're a person that abstracts all of
your finances, including budgeting and
spending for a lot of people. And you
know the the robo advisor market has
kind of consolidated around something
like 25 basis points of your assets. So
a quarter of a percent of all of your
assets are charged as fees typically.
Some are more, some are less. And full
service financial advice has been in
like the 1% plus range. And if I had to
guess, probably there's some middle
ground where on average as more AI tools
come in and start to blur these two. I I
think it'll probably consolidate to
somewhere in between. Really quick, I
got a fun story here. I uploaded my
entire portfolio to Claude about a week
ago and I said, "Rate my portfolio. Tell
me everything I'm doing wrong or any
improvements." It gave me a whole list
and believe it or not, it saved me
$16,000
a year after tax because it said one of
the funds that I was holding was paying
a slightly higher expense ratio than a
near identical fund that I could buy
from Vanguard. Yeah. And it said if you
sell this fund, you could realize it was
a very small loss. Realize this tax
loss, move it into this other fund that
has a lower fee, and that fee works out
to $16,000 a year. I did it. I mean, I I
researched myself in addition to that,
but that pointed in the right direction.
It's like, wait a second, that's such a
no-brainer. I didn't think of that. I
just wasn't paying attention. There you
go. 16 grand a year saved.
>> Yeah. And I think for some for a lot of
things where it's it's really clearcut,
it it's super super useful, right? Like
um Yeah. If you have a fund with a high
expense ratio uh and there's a similar
fund with a lower one, of course, that's
a that's a straightforward one. Or, you
know, if you've got cash in a savings
account earning 0% and there's this
other account here that can get you
north of three, of course, the rational
thing is to move all of that cash. A lot
of that doesn't even need AI to be
honest. It's just a very very simple
algorithm to just see, you know, if you
if you have funds that are underutilized
and and can be moved elsewhere. So, a
lot of our investors ask us about this
like cash sorting AI idea, which is,
>> you know, is in the future is the AI
just going to move your cash to places
that have
>> high interest? Um,
>> oh, eventually you'll lose track of
that. Oh gosh, imagine if it just
>> Well, my thought is that's not even AI.
You can just have a screen that says,
well, and and we try to do this. Hey, we
offer 3.5% APY. you could be, you know,
you could be making incrementally tens
of thousands of dollars per year just by
doing this. Um, and and despite the fact
that those products exist, people still
like their legacy banks and, you know,
banks still have trillions of assets
that are earning almost zero because,
you know, the the inertia and the
strength of that relationship is is so
high. Do you think investing will
fundamentally change when everyone is
using like a AI investing agent and
these AI agents can t tap into all
publicly available information
instantly? And so like it it
automatically just knows like is that
sometime down the time horizon? If so,
like how long? Or do you think that's
just not even feasible?
>> There's lots of different investing
behaviors. I don't think that
someone who is buying a stock of a
company that makes a product uh they use
is going to be all of that all that
affected by AI. If you're like I use the
iPhone, great product, I believe in it.
I want to own some Apple stock. AI is
unlikely to change that investment
behavior significantly. What are you
going to ask it? Right? I mean, maybe if
you're really kind of having second
thoughts and you're not sure whether
it's a good one, you'll ask some
questions. But by and large, I I think
that that's um uh that's durable. Active
trading, I think active trading is going
to look significantly different. A lot
of active trading is now geared towards
technical analysis on charts. AI tools
will certainly augment that quite a bit.
Um and then you can bring in more data
sources.
uh passive long-term investing and
portfolio construction. Yeah, I don't
think it'll change very much because
in that particular example, it's really
about making a infrequent asset
allocation decision. And may maybe
you'll have more data communicating the
decision and what's going on, which is
what we're doing with Robin Hood
products, like what's going on in your
portfolio? Why did we make those
changes? Um, but I think fundamentally
the the the asset allocation process has
been automated and streamlined pretty
well and I I don't think there's juice
there. So, yeah, it's it's really
trading. I think trading is where you're
going to see the biggest change and and
the biggest disruption, which is why
we're focused on agentic trading first.
>> What about for productivity within Robin
Hood as a company? How much has AI
changed the game? I changed it uh very
deeply. I mean I think our AI adoption
is close to 100%. If you're a software
engineer and really software engineers
are building all the products. I think
the the workflow has shifted from,
you know, humans writing the code and
humans reviewing the code to generally
humans overseeing agents uh and and
those agents are writing the code and
reviewing the code. and your job as an
engineer is shifting to making sure your
agents are well managed and and seeing,
you know, how many agents you can employ
and can you keep them busy all the time,
including when you're sleeping.
>> So, do you think though with Robin Hood
eventually you could have just a few
people running the entire company from
home?
>> It's not our goal for sure. Um
uh I I think sometimes we do um we do
think about these things. Um
but I think that someone still has to be
running the agents and at the end of the
day it's like my financial fiduciary
point. Uh it's hard to imagine
a world where a human is not like
responsible for decisions.
>> Yeah. And so I think we've been we've
been focused on doing more with the
teams that we have and and giving people
more leverage. Um but yeah, less focused
on just reducing headcount.
>> What's the biggest mistake that you've
made over the last year?
>> You know, I'm I'm sure I've made lots of
little mistakes. I think my my my
approach to things is really just how
can I move forward? like I don't like
thinking about the past very much. I
think we can kind of get stuck
relitigating decisions, but um really
it's it's about okay, where are we now?
You know, I I even in some cases prefer
to be behind and to be an underdog cuz I
think it gives us something to work
towards and and to really push on. I
mean the past year if I had to think
about what we've done okay uh for active
traders we've launched prediction
markets and that that's a interesting
business for us because usually we're
not the first to launch a new asset
class you know equity trading was a
thing for multiple decades even
electronically before Robin Hood came
along we improved it we we brought it to
the smartphone we brought it to zero
commission, but you know, we we weren't
early to it. Crypto trading, we weren't
particularly early either. I mean, we
launched in 2018,
which was early relative to the Trady
companies,
>> but a lot of cryptonative companies
started in 2012 or even earlier.
Bitstamp, which we acquired, was, you
know, I think the longest continuously
running crypto exchange. So, we were we
were uh not the earliest there.
prediction markets. We were one of the
first to to roll out that product as
soon as they got legalized for the
presidential election. We were kind of
there within weeks with a product and
then we had to really expanded over time
and
>> uh you know it's it's it's grown to
hundreds of millions of annual revenue
or fastest growing business line of all
time. Um so active traders we've done
well. Banking uh has been a really quick
roll out. I think that the challenge
that I'm spending a lot of time thinking
about is now that we're doing all of
these things, how can we make sure the
core experience is coherent? And we've
been investing a lot more in
personalization in making like the app
clean. And you know, I can say, well,
maybe maybe I should have thought more
about these problems earlier, but a year
ago, we probably didn't have so many new
products shipping. So
>> that's what I've noticed as a daily
user, probably hourly user of Robin Hood
app. Every time I log on, it's like
there's more things to swipe through.
And a lot of [clears throat] the things
I'm not using, but what I find really
interesting is you guys launch the
prediction markets,
>> but then people could just email
customer support and then say, "Hey, can
you like remove this from my account?"
And I know people that have actually
gotten that removed from their account
both for the simplification and also
because they don't want to be involved
with prediction markets, which I found
really interesting. you guys were able
to like engineer the app for a specific
user experience, which is like I mean
like I don't know of I can't name
another company that can that would that
would do that.
>> Yeah. Yeah. And and now at first it used
to be customer support and now you can
actually like flip a switch if you want
prediction markets uh to Nacho Sports
and also a lot of our core surfaces. It
used to be that, you know, Robin Hood
had only a couple types of accounts. We
had, you know, your brokerage account,
crypto, retirement, spending. Each of
those accounts were kind of their own
tab,
>> but not a lot of not everyone used
retirement, not everyone used crypto. A
and there's another problem of well, we
added 13 additional accounts, right? Um
so we had to completely redesign things
around this idea that you know every tab
in the app should have a use case for
every customer. So now we have like
investment watch list search account and
it's taken a lot of iteration to find
the solution that is optimal because
every change you make affects tens of
millions of existing customers. So it's
highly consequential. I do want to say
just because I absolutely loved this,
not that it will necessarily lead to any
conversation, but I love the fact that
you can open up multiple individual
investing accounts. Yeah. Like ever
since you guys had that, like I it has
completely changed the game for me
because now I don't have one strategy in
one account and you know like or
multiple strategies all consolidated to
one account like that and the UI for it
is like from a user experience
phenomenal. I am curious though on the
personality trait of not of not
litigating prior decisions. Do you think
that that's an essential trait of an
effective CEO?
>> Not necessarily. I think uh a lot of
people
uh a lot of I and and I should make it
seem I I shouldn't make it sound like I
don't really think about you know what
happened in the past. Of course, we do
postmortems and reviews and things of
that nature, but I think a lot of people
just um
live in the past and spend, you know,
80% of time worrying about things that
have already happened. Um and a little
bit less time thinking about, okay, what
what do we do now? I try always to think
about the current state and what my
options are rather than saying, oh, if
if I had changed this 6 months ago,
things would have been different. I
think it's also impossible to a certain
extent to think through
what would have happened if you'd done
something differently in the past
because there's just so many inputs in
in those decisions you know like
>> it's a trap sort of
>> it's a trap and yeah things are the
important things are never clean in the
sense that oh if I had just like uh made
this one decision differently
my entire life since that point would
have been uh would have been different a
lot People say that you are one of the
most effective CEOs and founders alive
today, which I I mean I mean you see it
all over X.
>> Wow, that's humbling.
>> Well, it probably feels cool to know
that. If you were to distill that job
description down to one thing, I could
see it being problem solver. And so, I
mean, would you agree with that
sentiment? Running a podcast is honestly
a lot more work than people may think.
From sponsor contracts and invoices and
clipping, it piles up so quickly. I'm
not kidding when I say we literally use
Claude for everything now and that's why
we are so excited to be partnering with
them. Claude is the AI for problem
solvers. It's the collaborator that
understands your entire workflow and
thinks with you, not for you. Whether
you're debugging code at midnight,
building a financial model, or
strategizing your next business move.
Claude extends your thinking to tackle
the problems that matter. And Cork goes
way beyond the chatbot. It's not
answering questions. It's actually doing
the work. real spreadsheets, formatted
reports, organized files directly on
your computer with no uploads and no
cleanup. Plus, Claude's newest model,
Fable 5, is live and ready to help you
solve your most complex problems. For
us, it was actually taxes. We uploaded
our bank statements and Fable 5 went
through every document incredibly fast
and gave us an organized spreadsheet
that was ready to send straight to our
accountant. It saved us hours, if not at
this point, days. We also use Claude for
generating invoices, writing emails,
titling videos, setting up test
projects, and even editing videos for
our clips channel. The sheer amount of
time and money that we have saved from
using Claude for our business is just
unreal. I kid you not. Literally
yesterday, I was on the phone with my
dad driving to pickall and I said, "Dad,
sign up for the Claude Max plan, upload
all of your financial statements, and
Claude will literally pay for itself
with the amount of value it gives you."
You should definitely see what tasks you
can take off your plate with Claude. For
problems worth solving, get started with
Claude at claud.ai/icedcop.
That's claude.ai/iced
coffee and check out Claude Pro, which
includes access to all the features
mentioned in today's episode.
Claude.ai/icced
coffee. AI is going to transform your
business. Look, we've all heard this,
but if you've actually rolled it out in
your company, you know how this usually
goes. You make the investment, everyone
gets onboarded, and a few months later,
no one's using it, including you. Well,
thankfully today's sponsor, Superhuman
Go, is actually built to stick.
Superhuman Go is an AI chat that sits
right on the side of your browser, ready
to help with any task you're working on.
It's actually from the makers of
Grammarly, and it works inside the tools
and sites your team already uses.
Whatever's on your screen, an email, a
doc, a website. It already knows what
you're looking at. You're not opening
new tabs, pasting stuff in, or
explaining yourself from scratch. All
you have to do is ask and it'll
summarize a long email thread, draft you
a reply, or prep you for a meeting
without you spending hours. It also
searches across all of your tools, so
you're not clicking through five
different apps trying to remember where
something is.
>> Plus, since nobody has to learn anything
new, everyone on the team ends up using
it. It's the easiest way to get AI into
your business. So, if you're finally
done paying for tools that nobody
touches, give Superhum Go a shot. To
find out more, just go to superhum.com.
Again, that is superhum.com or click the
link down below in the description to
get started. Thank you again to
Superhuman Go for supporting the
podcast. A lot of people say that you
are one of the most effective CEOs and
founders alive today, which I I mean I
mean you see it all over X.
>> Wow, that's humbling.
>> Well, it probably feels cool to know
that if you were to distill that job
description down to one thing, I could
see it being problem solver. And so I
mean would you agree with that
sentiment?
>> I think it depends on the company. I
think the job kind of changes
dramatically depending on what you're
responsible for. So I'll give you an
example.
If the company is small and you're the
CEO and you're just trying to like ship
your one product to customers and make
sure it works, the job is really how
quickly can I ship code, right? That's
essentially the problem. Uh if if you
think about it on a base level, problem
solver probably does fit. But problem is
a very broad term. So small company, how
much code can I ship? And I went through
this evolution myself because when when
I started at Robin Hood, I was writing a
lot of code. Then you kind of get to a
point where, okay, maybe we have to do
two products at a time and it's not just
shipping them, but marketing them,
designing them, right? Uh
>> and and there you're kind of leading a
small team of engineers and maybe
dealing with a couple of domains that
aren't really in your core competency.
And I think the challenge there is how
do you stay close enough to the work
that's being done by the folks that
you're managing and also learn enough to
be useful about these other domains that
you're not an expert in. Right? And a
lot of times it's just can you put in
the hours and sort of like the mental
effort to learn about things that aren't
your core competency. A lot of engineers
don't really have an interest in
learning about marketing or legal or ops
and and I think it's limiting because
if if you don't know anything about the
domain, how can you actually make
improvements, right? or you you have to
know enough to like realize what's
working, what's not working, what you
can change. And then you know at every
layer of scale it becomes
um yeah it becomes harder in a sense
because you have more groups of people
working on things that you're less
directly involved in. And there it's
about building systems. Okay. How can I
efficiently if if I wanted to spend like
five minutes on something, how can I get
the best and highest signal five minutes
possible? What are the tools to do that?
Do I have the metrics? Do I have
customer verbatims? Do I have just like
AI tools that are plugged into the right
data so that you know you can actually
make every second that you spend on
something as like high signal and useful
as it could be and so that you're not
kind of making decisions based on
anecdote. So a lot of it is building
these systems organizing things
effectively so that you kind of know the
person to ask or to probe if something's
going wrong or you have a question. and
also
spending time on on the right things.
>> That's fascinating. I mean, effectively,
you just distilled down the blueprint of
like building a huge company and like
how to organize your life as an operator
or executive. If you were to identify
one trait or belief that a lot of
operators have that are not working at
maximum efficiency, like something
that's sort of holding them back, what
similarity do you see among those
people? like what should the the the
primary question CEOs, operators,
executives should be asking themselves
in order to become more effective?
>> I think one is
um
being able to get into the details of
every team, every work stream. Um, and
you know, a lot a lot of people just
rely on
assessments of people in management,
right? But sometimes it's really helpful
to get both ends both ends of the
barbell so to speak, you know, the the
senior executive's view of a situation
and also the people on the ground cuz
you you could have the problem of like
if if something breaks somewhere up in
the chain and bigger organizations, this
is a problem. if you have like
individual contributors, managers,
directors, senior directors, you know,
if something's broken in the chain, um
you could get bad information about
what's happening. So that's why I I find
it very helpful sometimes to go as close
to the ground as possible. You know,
look at the code, be able to look at the
code, look at the actual copy that's
shipping to the website, talk to people
who are individual contributors or
interns. spend a lot of time talking to
interns. Um, and so, so I think being
able to get extremely deep into the
details is important. Not a lot of
people do that. And that goes to the
work. I think the other thing is just uh
hiring well, making sure that the people
around you um in my case, it's like the
the general managers and the functional
leads are incredibly strong. And I think
I've been fortunate to evolve to a place
where it's just of incredibly capable
people that are running really big
businesses and growing uh alongside the
businesses that they're running.
>> You know, it's a hilarious parallel to
draw there, like staying close to the
problem. So, we have a friend, his name
is Ben Mala, and he buys huge commercial
apartment complexes or just commercial
real estate. like he just bought a new
place that's like hundreds of units and
he gets his son to move into the complex
to be close to the problem to know what
it's like to actually be a resident at
the complex to know where to make
improvements where to spend money to
have the highest possible return on
quality of life for the residents there.
And that's kind of similar to what
you're saying here. It's like you need
to talk to everybody in the food chain.
You need to get like the executive
opinion as well as like the the person
who's actually going and like you know
assembling the product's opinion.
>> Yeah. And also you need to talk to the
customer and it it's both the customers
that are loud on Twitter, the ones that
are loud on customer support, which are
not always the same. You need to look at
what the Redditors are saying, you know,
on the on the different subreddits. But
also, there's a lot of customers that
are quiet and will just silently stop
using the product and aren't going to go
talk talk about it to social on social
media or write in a support ticket. So,
you have to figure out how to get to
those customers, too. I think it it
really helps to be obsessed with your
business, right? Um, and and to really
feel like, you know, every little
problem
is just going to be on my mind until I
figure out uh a way to solve it. And,
you know, if I figured out a way to
solve it and it's actioned, then I can
kind of put it away in a little drawer,
check up on it later. But, um, I think
something I've noticed about myself is
I spend a lot of time obsessing about
every little detail. And I think in some
cases that can be annoying and sort of
uh
not ideal for maybe staying calm and and
having great mental health, but I think
is actually really really good for the
business.
>> What's the next thing you want to do
that regulation currently blocks?
>> Oh, that's a great question. I'm sure
the the regulators will love that one.
Uh
>> yeah, I mean I think generally we've had
really really strong constructive
relationships with the regulators. um
particularly in the last couple of years
where um yeah they've been they've been
much more keen to support innovation. I
think that the couple of things that
have been
sort of like fresh
new issues and you know one of the other
things we're doing now is we're we're
starting to think about how we can push
change in in all these policies um
rather than just being a participant in
them, right? uh PDT rule. You guys might
be familiar. That rule change came in.
We're very supportive of that. So, this
is a rule where if you don't have
$25,000 in your account, there's
restrictions to day trading.
>> Yeah. So that being repealed was was
very very good because essentially what
it did was it penalized customers that
uh didn't have a lot of money in their
accounts which you know a lot of
customers start with us so they don't
have a lot of money in their accounts
and they get into these situations where
um the intent of the rule was probably
to prevent them from making rash
decisions but then then you get into a
situation where you know if you like
want to close your position for a
riskmanagement reason it gets flagged as
a day trade. Then you get restricted and
you basically have to make that
decision. You intend to do it and you uh
you turn to another broker because
actually the other weird thing about
this rule is it's on a per broker basis.
So if you're a pattern day trader
somewhere, you can move your account
elsewhere and then
>> you start you sort of start from
scratch.
>> So that was a great positive change.
Couple of other things that I'm quite
keen on. Uh, one, accredited investor.
And since we last spoke, we've really
been pushing on the idea that private
ownership is kind of the next frontier
of our mission. Uh, for for various
reasons, but the main one like there's a
lot of disruption by AI. A lot of the
top AI companies like OpenAI and
Anthropic, for instance, are private.
They're going into the trillions of val
of dollars of valuation and there's a
small circle of wealthy insiders that's
benefiting from all the growth. It's not
broadly distributed.
So our solution to that make it easy to
own these companies um or get exposure
to them. In in the US we have Robin Hood
Ventures which essentially you can think
of as a basket of private companies
right and we we have Robin Hood Ventures
fund one which started with late stage
uh preIPO open AAI is is actually in
that fund
>> and it gave um a lowcost vehicle for
investing and getting exposure to
private companies
>> and and kind of on the heels of RVI we
started RV2 to Robin Hood Ventures Fund
2, which takes another angle. Uh, it's
still a basket of private companies, but
rather than them being ultra late
immediately preIPO kind of companies, we
went to the opposite side of the
spectrum and now we're giving exposure
to seed and series A, which is the
earliest stage of capital formation. So
rather than tens and hundreds of
billions valuations in these companies,
Robin Hood Ventures Fund 2 typical
valuations are in the tens of millions.
>> How do you pick those companies and what
if they don't want to be a part of them?
>> Yeah, great question and this is one of
the things we figured out uh this year.
Um
we uh have taken the position that uh if
a company doesn't want to be in Robin
Hood Ventures uh we we generally won't
force them. So, every deal that we've
done for Robin Hood Ventures thus far,
>> and this isn't true of some of our
competitors, of which there are a
couple, some of our competitors will go
in and do the second layer SPVLP
interest and, you know, then announce it
and then you've seen the company come in
and say, "Actually,
we don't know anything about this." Uh,
not ideal. So with Robin Hood Ventures,
we've taken the position that we go
direct with the company's blessing in
all of these cases. And that's true of
all the deals that we've done thus far.
Um, and I think this was not an obvious
one, right? Because there's a trade-off.
What you really want is the access, but
you also are creating a new product and
you want that new product to
>> uh be accepted by the stakeholders in
the industry. What if we take it a step
further and we say that everyone gets
access to these private privatized
companies? Then wouldn't it be that the
really wealthy people just get in even
sooner?
>> There's always a cat and mouse game in
the sense that uh the the wealthy always
figure out how to get better things and
so our job is never done right. Then we
have to uh we have to keep working to
get even earlier access
>> and then they get in a little earlier
too. But I mean, look, Robin Hood
Adventure 2 seed series A uh that that's
like pretty early. It's it's hard to get
earlier. And we're partnering with YC
for that fund. So, I think we'll prove
out the model of seed and series A
funding for retail. Um now, the problem
with these things is these are still
baskets, right? And what we're hearing
from customers is maybe I like these
three companies, but I don't like these
other three. So, I think the end state
is going to be investing and trading for
those that want to uh individual private
names
>> so that they feel pretty close to what
trading a public stock on Robin Hood
would feel. And and that part needs both
continued product innovation and also
reform of accredited investor standards
which now limit direct investments to
private companies to high earning
wealthy people.
>> Is there any other product that you wish
existed? Like for me I wish that you
guys had or someone created a Venmo
where we could send each other stocks
like instead of sending Jack a hundred
bucks they'd be like yo here's $100 of
Google.
>> Yeah. And you know, last time you guys
asked me for Robin Hood social, right?
Uh and I said, "Oh, well, maybe uh we'll
have something to announce in the
future." And
>> you know, he said to me, the audacity of
Graham to say this, he was all he was
all, you know, didn't we say something
about a Robin Hood social last time and
then they launched it and I was like, if
you think that because you suggested
Robin Hood social afterwards, Vlad was
like, "Yo, let's do it. Let's launch it.
Let's launch it."
>> Um Yeah. Yeah. No, I thought it was
funny cuz obviously uh it it had been in
the works. You know, we we we didn't
just whip it up. Broke
>> his heart.
>> We didn't just whip it up in a couple of
weeks uh from from when uh we had that
conversation to Hood Summit when we
announced it. But um yeah, there's
always sometimes I get asked about
things in the works and um I really want
to like spill the beans right there, but
then I'm like, "Ah, well, we have these
events, we're launching things."
>> So, if we just keep guessing, you just
wouldn't say no. You can tell based on
my reaction probably what's in the works
or not. Uh even though I try to keep a
very very calm poker face, but you know,
Robin Hood social has done well. And now
I don't know if you guys are seeing it,
but people have started cross-osting
>> Robin Hood social screenshots on X.
>> Yeah. And they're like, "What's going on
in this community?" And that's bringing
in more.
>> People need to be verified, by the way,
because my profile is up there. And I
think uh people think that I'm a scammer
on Robin Hood social because they don't
have a check mark. Like there's no way
to verify that is actually your
username. Graham Stefen.
>> Okay. I'm J L S L B Y. Follow us on
Robin Hood social, guys.
>> Oh well.
>> Yeah, but that means someone else is
going to create one that's very similar.
>> Uh and then they're going to like start
like scamming. I don't know.
>> We'll have to figure this out. Okay.
Yeah. I mean, the one thing that we
think works really well with Robin Hood
Social is the fact that the trades and
the portfolios are verified and you
know, now we have P&L widgets and all
these things. So in in other social
media platforms where people are sharing
your trades, you don't really know
whether they're BSing or they could be
faking the screenshots. With Robin Hood
social, we kind of take care of that
verification as part of the platform
which I think has like uh had a really
nice it's a it's a positive and also
differentiated aspect. But yeah, we'll
we'll obviously have to solve this
verification problem for for the
profiles as well. Is there any financial
product that's not really being
discussed though? Because as someone
who's so on the pulse with customer
demand and just broad investing data,
there has to be like whispers of some
sort of investment style. Like no one
thought five maybe 10 years ago that we
would have AI investing agents. Yeah.
Right. But someone may have and I feel
like you would probably be the person of
of all to ask like what could the future
of finance look like? Something we may
not even be talking about right now in 5
to 10 years. Is there some sort of
product or service or like something
else?
>> Yeah, I mean Robin Hood chain I think is
a is a good example of what the future
could be if we could like rebuild the
infrastructure from the ground up. I
don't know if you guys are familiar with
Robin Hood chain. It's it's basically
the hottest chain in crypto right now.
We rolled it out a couple of weeks ago
and it's been top five in DEX volume. uh
the TVL total value locked has been
growing tremendously and uh one of the
benefits is it has stock tokens which
are tokenized representations of stocks
that are available for customers outside
the US for now but you know you're
they're still available in 120 plus
countries around the world and if you're
on Robin Hood chain and you have stock
tokens like Tesla Nvidia or others you
actually can do
everything with them that you could do
with uh another onchain crypto. So, you
can send them to people onchain just
like you would send Bitcoin or Ethereum.
You can swap them in pools. Uniswap has
uh some very very active pools on Robin
Hood chain. You can do uh
collateralization, lending, and
borrowing. So, you you get a picture of
what it could look like if we kind of
replaced it all with software. So, when
you say swapping, does that mean that
let's just say I have $500,000 worth of
gains in a stock that I could swap that
stock for another, keeping my cost basis
without realizing a gain?
>> The tax situation depends on where you
are, right? Every every one of these 120
countries has slightly different tax
treatments. So, I can't really speak
generally to that. Um but yeah all all
you have to do is create a pool. If
someone creates a pool exchanging you
know a stock token with a crypto uh yeah
you can just swap them directly. So we
started out using stablecoin. So USDG
which is the stable coin that we
partnered with Paxos and a few others to
launch. that's like the the core stable
coin of the chain. But then all the
developers have created all kinds of
unique pools that we didn't even think
would exist and and all kinds of
protocols where for example if you hold
a memecoin you just get uh stock tokens
uh air dropped to you. Right. So they've
like connected meme coins, core cryptos,
and the stock tokens and composed them
into into unique products that yeah, we
we wouldn't have anticipated creating,
we probably wouldn't have thought of to
make ourselves. So it's it's um Robin
Hood chain is this combination of
developer platform with uh financial
primitives uh like high yield and stock
tokens that we're going to add to and
and I think the combination of those two
is going to lead to a lot of interesting
things. Not to mention you know late it
was built for AI agents too. So a lot of
people have been rolling out APIs
command line interfaces. I'm just
imagining if you tried explaining this
to Warren Buffett,
>> like what he would say, like if if this
is even something he would understand,
it would say, "No, this is just
>> I mean, I think to to most consumers who
aren't developers,
uh the value prop is really if you're in
120 countries all over anywhere in the
world. uh if you have a smartphone,
internet connection, you can trade uh
tokenized representations of these
stocks 24/7
uh at relatively low cost and great user
experience.
>> But then even if you're a US resident,
then you can be trading outside of
trading hours all day like it
effectively opens up the optionality of
a of a investor.
>> Yeah. So right now they're not available
in the US but there has been movement to
enable tokenization here and I I think
eventually it will happen.
It's just the the delta in value is is
much smaller. It it would be like
>> you know in a lot of these places
overseas they don't even have functional
banking systems. So they can go right to
>> uh
>> tokenized stocks and it's a huge leap,
right? Whereas in the US you already
have Robin Hood. So going from Robin
Hood to like 24/7 is comparatively
minor. It would be like going from your
very fast train to a high-speed train,
right? Uh expensive shift. Uh a lot of
the existing train operators aren't keen
to make the investment and you can
already get from New York to DC in 2
hours. So shaving it to 1 hour maybe
maybe isn't the biggest delta. And so I
think that's why the rest of the world
is leading here and the US is probably
going to be a late adopter of of some of
these technologies.
>> What do you think the other brokerages
fail to understand about investing in
2026? Now really quick I got to say that
everyone has a business idea that
they've been sitting on. And what stops
most people really isn't the idea
itself. It's everything that comes after
it. We're talking building the store,
taking payments, the checkout page, but
it's actually very straightforward when
our partner Shopify handles it for you.
Everything that you need to start
selling is included and ready from day
one. That includes the moment your first
customer is ready to pay. Shopify
checkout helps more of them actually
finish their purchase. Plus, when they
come back, their details are already
saved. It's one tap and they're done.
I've personally used Shopify several
times because before I was working with
Graham, I set up probably five or six
different Shopify stores and even me
actually saw some sales and I knew
absolutely nothing. Shopify is genuinely
the easiest way to start an online brand
and see real sales coming in. Shopify
powers millions of businesses worldwide.
From household names like Mattel and Gym
Shark to small everyday businesses just
getting started. With Shopify, nothing
stands between your idea and a real
business. So go make it one. Start a
free trial at shopify.com/ic.
Once again, that is shopify.com/ic.
One more time, that's shopify.com/ic
with the link down below in the
description to get started. What do you
think the other brokerages fail to
understand about investing in 2026? I
think the other brokerages suffer from
just being large. I I mean, I think
there's a lot of players in the space,
right? There's the incumbents that are
big and they have tens of trillions in
assets. But yeah, I think we we ship
much much faster and we're more modern,
which means that we've been able to
capture a younger customer base that uh
is growing wealthier over the next
couple of decades as opposed to aging
out. And so we're kind of the
beneficiary of this great wealth
transfer over time. So, if you were a
paid consultant to the other brokerages,
what would you tell them?
>> I think to some degree, um, it starts
with talent. Like, if if you want to
build really really great products that
are competitive and 10 times better than
um
what's already out there. Um there there
needs to be like a talent reset and you
have to make sure really good engineers
and designers and product builders,
people that understand AI are in the
company. Um so I I would probably find
one area and these companies are like
giant elephants, right? You can't eat
the elephant in one bite as they say.
You have to you have to just
>> take it one one bite at a time. You you
eat it very slowly. So, I'd probably
find one area
which maybe was small and kind of
circumscribed away from the core and and
try to like inject a ton of talent into
that one area. Run it kind of standalone
separately and see if that can
provide a road map how of of how we can
do like a technology transformation for
the entire company. And so if we get a
beach head in one area and we're able to
hire special forces, elite talent there,
um then we kind of like put more into
there and and see that grow till
eventually the the entire company is
rebuilt with a stronger foundation.
>> In terms of the broader economy, are you
worried about valuations?
>> I think in some sectors
alarm bells have started ringing. I I'll
give you an example. I mean, we get a
lot of feature requests from our
customers all the time, right? And for
the longest time, international stocks
was not in the top 10. I mean, some
people wanted international stocks,
>> but you know, a couple maybe maybe a
month or two ago, every question I would
get in interview was, "When are you
going to add Korean stocks?" That's what
everyone wants. You know, nobody wants
>> Mhm.
>> prediction markets or crypto. Uh, we
just want Korean stocks. I don't know if
you guys experienced this.
>> Very familiar with what's going on.
>> Or were you some of the people that were
asking asking for them?
>> Probably Jack, [laughter]
>> I'll invest in anything.
>> Yeah. And and by the way,
>> as long as they do options on Korean
stocks, I end.
>> And by the way, we will add Korean
stocks. But the fact that we were
hearing from
>> so many people at the same time does
raise the alarm bells a little bit of
like what's going on there. And sure
enough, yes, there was just
>> So, what are you seeing today? Starting
to ring some bells.
>> Yeah. And I have to be careful here
because I'm not uh I I don't want to
give people investment advice. Um and
also to be fair, traditionally our
customers
>> are
>> like innovation first. So, we were among
the first to invest in electric
vehicles. They're obviously into crypto
AI even though, you know, um exposure
directly to AI labs is difficult and
we're fixing it with Robin Hood
Ventures, you've got the semiconductors
and and now you've got a lot of people
talking about energy, right? So
>> um I guess chips and energy as a
category
you have uh you have a very very
complicated balancing act to play cuz on
the one hand it is kind of obvious if
you assume uh people are saying well if
AI demand continues to grow of course
that's going to impact chips and
everything in the stack underneath it.
On the other hand, what you have is the
traders, and this includes, you know,
there's been anecdotes of hedge funds
that are just buying chips because they
know, hey, even if I don't need this
chip myself, I'll be able to resell it
at a higher price. And whether something
is undervalued or not kind of depends on
many of these factors. And and I could
see it tipping in one direction. And you
know if it if a lot of the supply is
being bought by speculators that's when
you can kind of get into trouble with
you know even something that has
fundamental growth potential like uh
chips in an AI environment.
>> Do you think that a high stock market
right now is actually bad for people in
their 20s and 30s?
>> Everything I think is is an opportunity
in a sense. Um, back in 2020 when we had
a big crash right around COVID, you saw
our customers actually buying, you know,
and and you looked at the customers of
the other discount brokers and they were
selling and that was the big story. Our
customers were buying because they're
younger. They had uh a long-term horizon
and they saw it as an opportunity. they
were still fundamentally bullish about
the country and of all the things that
you know were were were being built and
and what the stock market offered and
they kind of showed that through their
activity on the platform in a sense a
lot of people say well do you worry
about stock market corrections
>> I don't worry about them as much because
we've seen in the past that having
younger customers they they take
corrections as opportunities now that
doesn't mean that I want a correction or
I even want you know a sustained period
of slightly lower prices that can be
very very challenging to the economy and
to people. Uh I think everyone generally
should just want things to go up
smoothly up and to the right but uh it's
not the reality and I think every market
environment if you're a trader presents
opportunities that you can capitalize on
and if you're a long-term investor it
can be hard to predict these things and
time them. So we offer great tools for
uh tax advantaged
>> investing. I think we have the best
retirement products on the market where
it's really targeted towards putting
money in and you know not withdrawing
for many many decades. And and I think
uh dollar cost averaging and passive
management is better at Robin Hood than
at any of our competitors. You know a
lot of our competitors don't even offer
good tools for for these things. But
we're continuing to invest and
incentivize. A lot of people criticize
us because they think we incentivize
active trading and prediction markets.
If you look at what we actually
incentivize in the product, it's
retirement. Retirement gives you a 3%
match if you're a gold member and you
make a contribution. So those are the
types of products that we've really
directly incentivized and and had
success incentivizing. Now, what do you
say to the people who criticize that it
is leaning too heavy into prediction
markets which might be considered too
close to gambling?
>> Yeah, we get that criticism and of
course you mentioned the switcher and
being able to customize it. We get the
criticism in both directions actually.
Um, you know, we have people that just
don't want to see prediction markets.
And for that, we have personalization
and all the initiatives we have, not
just for you to disable it, but also to
make sure that we show you the content
that you want to see in the app when you
want to see it. It's a it's a big
priority not just with prediction
markets but also the more different
products and features we have. We have
to solve the problem of you just not
being aware of us offering a great
feature that you can benefit from. Um so
yeah there's there's both I don't want
to see this product prediction markets
being a great example. Also, I want to
see it more like it's too buried in the
product and I don't want it to be, you
know, three taps away. I just want to
see what's going on right now. And I
think personalization is an answer. Uh
the other thing we've been experimenting
with is in some cases if really the
experience is very very different, uh we
break it out into a separate app, which
is what we did with banking. So if you
want like a a banking and a card
experience, you can have that in the
banking app. If you want a more trading
first experience, you have like the main
green Robin Hood app. And if you want
full crypto, the Robin Hood wallet has
like DeFi native experience.
>> What do you think the critics are
getting right that you could improve on?
I mean, I think that um
making things cohesive and making the
purpose of the company and what we stand
for more understandable is is a fair
critique. We hear that a little bit.
Everyone always wants features and it's
hard for me. I mean, the the Korean
stocks, I think they're right. I think
we probably should have Korean stocks as
well as stocks for from every single
market. There's just a bunch of stuff
that we just haven't gotten to yet
because there's always more and more to
build. And the way that I think about
this is there's kind of three buckets of
thing, right? infrastructure
improvements that just make the ex
existing experience better like faster
performance like just better nicer
cleaner UI UX uh reliability so that we
just uh can handle traffic spikes better
and things like that and we we made
tremendous progress there even in the
past year actually there's the category
of like what's available at other
brokers that Robin Hood doesn't have and
that's It's a big category up until
recently. It's trust accounts. Uh
international stocks are available at
some of our competitors. You've got
things like fixed income if you want to
buy direct bonds, mutual funds. You
know, there's a lot of things that we
don't offer that are sizable parts of
portfolios of customers, right? And then
there's this third bucket which I think
can be easy to overlook.
Not a lot of people have products here,
but it's just like can we innovate and
can we be the first to market with with
new products relative to our peer set at
least. And that's where things like
prediction markets uh Robin Hood
ventures entirely net new product things
like Robin Hood chain and and Robin Hood
earn like we we also want to put things
in there that are completely unexpected.
Agentic trading we were talking about. I
mean, nobody
nobody big, no no no nobody non-trivial
is like working on aentic trading
besides us, right? Like we're just
figuring that out.
>> Slightly off topic, are you ever worried
about the billionaire tax here in
California?
>> I try not to think about it very much.
Um, yeah. Yeah. And again, it's it's one
of those things where um
Yeah. I mean, California has this
interesting kind of referendumbased
structure where if you get enough
support, um, even if the governor or
local politicians or, you know, the the
people support or are opposed to
something, you can get on the ballot
anyway. I think the predict we have a
prediction market on this.
>> So, you could hedge yourself in a way.
[laughter]
>> Technically, I could, although that's
not one of the deepest markets. Uh but
yeah, I think I think it's it's showing
it as a minority. So hopefully that does
hold.
>> What would change in your life if there
was a billionaire tax?
>> Well, a couple of things. Um
one,
I think the real risk isn't to me
personally, although obviously it would
not be amazing. Um it's to the ecosystem
here, right? Um,
so I think I think the real risk is it
could be like a own goal for California
because there's basically been two
industries that California hasn't just
been leading the country but has been
leading the world in many cases. One is
entertainment industry, Hollywood, uh,
and and that's just gotten decimated in
the past 10 years, right? and and a lot
of it is policy decisions, their own
goals, not giving incentives to people
to shoot and film and to hire people
locally. So then they're flying to
Atlanta or Canada or Eastern Europe. And
you know, it's hard to break this
network, but I think that what's
happened in Hollywood has shown that
that network can be broken. If you have
filming and studios moving elsewhere,
and then eventually the talent and the
directors and actors move elsewhere, and
then you get to a point where, you know,
they're not even having the award shows
in in LA because nobody lives there
anymore. So, I think there's a real
danger of that. Could that happen to the
technology industry? Um, I think it was
looking fairly bleak for technology in
San Francisco during COVID. People were
talking about moving to Texas, moving to
Florida, and AI kind of resuscitated
things.
>> But, um, I think what happened in LA
shows that we shouldn't take, uh, this
for granted. Yeah. But what what the
real risk is, you know, I think a lot of
people will nobody's going to want to be
taxed every single year, 5% of their
wealth. And these taxes do tend to start
uh very very popular, but then
eventually they cover everyone. Um, and
over time I think you could actually get
to a situation where the lost revenue
from people paying moderate taxes, um,
but doing them consistently is is much
higher than the one-time hit of like
taxing someone once and them leaving the
state. uh and a lot of people have
already left the state actually before
the the initial taxation would hit. So
even the threat of this happening has
been has been so severe that some people
have have bailed in relatively large
numbers pretty significant taxpayers.
>> If a billionaire tax passes on a
personal level, what would that do to
you? Would you just be forced to sell
some of your stake in your company? I
think it depends a lot on implementation
and some of it is uh yeah some some of
it hasn't been precisely
>> laid out
>> laid out um
yeah but I think a lot of people would
be forced to I mean the bulk of my
wealth is Robin Hood shares so um on a
cursory reading I think a lot of people
would have to sell shares in their
companies.
>> Do you keep your Robin Hood shares in
Robin Hood? Uh, no. Um, yeah.
>> Too many eggs [laughter] in one basket.
>> No, no, no. It's It's not because of
that. It's just because currently
>> you got a 3% AATS transfer fee to some
other. [laughter]
It's like, oh, wow.
>> That's I'm I'm I'm saving it for when uh
Yeah. for for rainy day. Um [laughter]
uh no because uh my shares and the
shares of our our um uh employees are
administered by um there's like special
requirements for how to administer
employee stock purchase plans and uh
what are called 10B51 plans which is I
can't just freely trade my Robin Hood
shares, right? I have to trade them
under a specific plan that's filed in
advance. Yeah. Because of material
non-public information.
>> Yeah, that makes sense. So, so there are
uh companies that deal with this uh and
it's like a B2B thing like I will
actually
uh I will actually create a deal with
you know a p a preo company to manage
their ESP to manage their 10b51s and I
become the the vendor.
>> Do you trade on Robin Hood?
>> I do. Yeah. So you you'll like wake up,
check the app, make a investment, but
also what's interesting is when you sign
up for Robin Hood, you have to check the
boxes that no one else does, right?
>> Like when I'm signing up for a new
brokerage, I say no, no, no, no. I don't
know anyone that's a 10% owner in a
company or this or that. Like I'm not
affiliated by any means with like
>> like I say no to all those disclosures,
but you actually have to say yes. How
does that change on a personal investing
way? I have to be really careful uh
trading individual stocks. I think ETFs
are uh are are pretty simple and pretty
clean. Uh crypto for a while I was doing
a lot of crypto because I love uh I love
crypto, right? I love trading. I love
like being in the trenches with people.
A lot of trenchers. Um I don't post on
Reddit anymore sadly
>> anymore. Okay. Uh yeah, at one point I
was a I was a Redditor uh early on in my
Robin Hood journey. I think I got off of
Reddit. Um but uh yeah, crypto has been
kind of nice because um yeah, it's it's
a it's a fun trading product. Futures
was nice when we launched it, prediction
markets as well, but yeah, individual
stocks. Um yeah, there's there's a lot
of restrictions. So,
>> what crypto do you have and own? Hey, by
the way, really quick. If you want extra
content just like this, as well as early
access and a bonus post show posted
every single week, feel free to join as
a channel member to get immediate access
to all of that, as well as early access
to everything else that we post along
with priority responses to all of your
comments. So, if that sounds cool, feel
free to join. Would love to have you on
board. Thanks so much. We'll get back to
the podcast now. What crypto do you have
and own? And again, I I don't want to
get into uh recommendations, but um I I
have a pretty diversified portfolio.
Yeah. To be honest with you.
>> Are you bullish on Bitcoin?
>> You know, Bitcoin is singular in a lot
of ways, which makes it special. It was
the first asset. It was the original
memecoin, right? The brand of it is is
quite strong because nobody can ever you
you can create lots of Bitcoin
imitators, but nobody can ever take the
position of being the first and and most
trusted. It's the, you know, main coin
that companies think about as they're
building out crypto treasuries to
diversify against inflation and and do
all sorts of things. So, yeah,
long-term, I'm bullish on Bitcoin. I
think it is singular and I think that
gives it an advantage over comparable
coins, but yeah, I can't tell you
>> if it's going to hit a million or
anything like that.
>> One thing I want to ask you is that
recently there was a Bitcoin hack with
the cold wallet and Bitcoin was stolen.
How do you make sure that if let's say I
deposit Bitcoin on Robin Hood that that
cryptocurrency is safe and that on your
end there couldn't be a hack or that
like there's an employee who just makes
a mistake who types in a wrong little
number and like something gets out there
and then
>> I think there's defense in depth what's
called defense in depth with with these
things. So without getting into the
exact details of our crypto custody
infrastructure um because there are a
lot of a lot of hackers out there um
>> you don't want to have too much of your
crypto easily accessible to people. Uh,
in fact, the lion share of it should be
in cold storage where you have to go and
like get pieces of paper ideally and not
exactly how it works, but it should just
be like not connected to the internet
and highly secure.
>> So, so that way even if there was
>> an issue with the hot wallet, it covers
a a very small minority of of crypto
assets. uh then you have to constantly
make sure that you're hardening your
infrastructure, you're watching out for
and preventing uh possible like security
breaches and incidents is very very
important for uh in this environment
because you have mythos and fable and
the AI tools are
>> if there is a vulnerability you can't
rely on
it being just hard to find or it being
too expensive. So that before AI tools,
it used to be that, you know, you
wouldn't have to worry as much because
you had to worry about these state
sponsored actors that would go after the
softest, largest targets.
>> Yeah.
>> And in reality, you know, there's much
there's banks that hold trillions of
assets that have poor relatively poor
cyber security posture. So they're just,
you know, being attacked everywhere. But
now, you know, it's so cheap to spin up
another job that you really have to make
sure that there's no holes. And I think
uh you have to do that with like
penetration testing, internal red
teaming, and also uh using the AI tools
themselves to scan and attack you like
they like they were an adversary. So I
think um we invest a lot in this and um
we're fortunate you know to to to be at
the frontier of a lot of these tools and
to actually um yeah spend a lot of
resources and a lot of our mind share in
in securing all these things and the I
think the surface area is always rising
right now we have Robin Hood chain we
have all of our DeFi products we have of
course the traditional business as well
as crypto so investing in security is a
huge priority. What are your personal
goals outside of Robin Hood?
>> I've really been focused on teaching my
kids math. I I still think math is
important. Um getting them to enjoy
learning and be curious. Uh so I um
whenever I get time to spend with them,
which is never as much as I would like,
but um I try to like talk to them about
history, uh encourage them to do math,
see how they're doing in school. I think
they have certain benefits
uh that I didn't have when I was a kid.
I mean, they could get access to the
best tutors. They could, you know, talk
to anyone they want. Um, and my concern
is always like how do you get the
benefits of that without the downsides?
And the downsides of growing up as my
kid is um like stuff can be easy for you
and maybe there's not the
>> incentive that I had to be hungry,
right? You know, if I if if I didn't
like work hard, my parents told me very
directly, we don't have the money to
send you to college. Very likely you're
going to have to get a scholarship,
which means you're going to have to do
all these things. And by the way, you
know, we were visa holders. So our
status in this country was very very
uncertain. There was always the threat
of okay, if you don't do well, maybe the
family will have to go back to Bulgaria,
right? Yeah. And I I think there's a
little bit less of that, which is good
in some ways, but but also it can be uh
it can be hard to like manufacture
hunger if it's not really there, right?
But yeah, I'm very proud of them
actually because despite this, I think
they're um yeah, they're they're growing
up to be great humans. Uh
yeah, other other goals I think about my
health. I'm getting a little older now,
so um I want to make sure that the body
and the mind is is working well because
I'd like to be
>> How do you do that? Do you do blood
testing, CT scans?
>> I've done the full body MRI thing. Um I
do blood testing. I just try to work out
uh regularly. I I've been getting into
like sauna and cold plunge and contrast
therapy. I also have been
trying really hard to have a routine
before I go to sleep cuz too easy for
me. I get into the thing of like
being on my phone or my iPad and just
looking at the company Slack or reading
docs till literally the last moment
before I close my eyes.
>> Yeah.
>> Like my phone just whacked me in the
head in bed. So what I'm trying to do
now is
journal a little bit for 10 to 15
minutes and then read a physical print
book for you know 15 to 20 minutes
before I go to sleep so that you know
things just get to to wind down a little
bit.
>> What kind of books do you read and have
you noticed an actual benefit from
journaling?
>> Yeah, I think the I have noticed a
benefit from journaling. You know, one
thing is
journaling for me, I have a little bit
of a structure to it. So, I write a
little bit about what happened in the
day or sometimes I do like a Sunday
journaling where I I think about the
whole week, the the week behind and then
the week forward. So, again, breaking my
rule of not thinking about the past. I
do think about the past um but just in a
way that helps me inform what I want to
do in the future either today or the
following week. What I like to do is I
think about the period in question. What
went well? I write those things down.
Those make me feel good. What could have
gone better? And then I I say, "Okay, if
I had to do some things this week,
here's the the list." And the list can
be quite long, right? It's like I want
to get 10 things, but then I sort them
based on what's the most important. Um,
and then I look back on the last one,
see how I did, and certain things I
carry over. Other things I say, "Hey, I
actually finished this. This is
awesome." But then, um, yeah, I have I
have a list of the week ahead and the
day ahead. And what happens is
when I wake up the next morning, I kind
of look it over and then I feel really
good
uh starting my day. I think what can be
a source of stress is just being
completely input driven and you kind of
wake up in the morning and you're like,
"Let me look at what other people want
from me, right? What are the fires? Are
there any emergencies? What are people
texting me about?" And then um yeah, the
risk is you just don't get the important
things done. So I think this at least
forces me to think about what the
important things are and make sure that
I'm aware if they got done or if they
didn't get done and and it helps them
get done as well. That's interesting to
be more output driven. It's like signal
and noise. It's like always said in all
of these different ways. And they say
one of the main sources of happiness is
feeling like you're in control of your
own destiny. And that translated to this
is basically like what must I do for
myself and for my business as opposed to
what fires do I need to respond to? It's
like you're not you're no longer in
control of your life if all you're ever
doing is responding to things and
external stimulus. Oh well, there's a
fire over here on this side of the
business. Let me tend to this as opposed
to like here's where I'm at. This is
what I'm going to do and I'm going to
push for this.
>> Yeah. I think a a big source of
unhappiness is to kind of feel like
things are out of your control even
though they aren't. Even, you know, some
of some of the some of my fondest
memories looking back are when I
went through some kind of crisis, right?
And and I went through the crisis and I
think back about
what was going through my mind at that
time. And you know, now with the benefit
of distance, I'm like, "Oh, that was a
really interesting time." It almost
seems fun in retrospect because now now
I appreciate it. But at that time, I was
really stressed out, right? Not enjoying
it at all, not sleeping. Um, and you
know, I think about how much better
would it be to actually have been
enjoying it or or be in a state of flow
at the time. E even though a lot of
crises are something happens that you
have to deal with but I think even those
things um are under your control at the
end of the day because whether you're
happy or not or motivated or in a state
of flow really depends on your mindset
as you're processing these things. In
terms of raising your children, do you
feel like math is more important than
social skills or are social skills going
to be more important in a world where AI
could do just about any math imaginable?
>> Did you see that Peter Teal thing? He
was uh he was asked about this a couple
years ago and he said, well, you know,
at the time math or AI was
>> getting really good at writing, right?
and you could just oneshot a history
essay um with just a simple prompt. And
so the conventional wisdom was, okay,
the math skills were going to be very
very important, but gosh, writing essays
or copywriting, be worried about that.
He said, "Oh, no. Uh, I'm much more
worried about the math people than the
word people." Because for the longest
time, actually, um,
word people were dominant in society,
but only recently has math been, um, a
prized skill set. And um yeah, by and
large he basically put the reason uh for
this basically on wokeness, right?
Because math is egalitarian in the sense
that you know you could actually test
different populations for mathematical
ability and you have outliers
no matter what your income is. But for
verbal ability and words and you know
how well read you are it does skew quite
heavily towards
you know people that have higher net
worth and socioeconomic status. So the
past uh
50 years or so, maybe even a little bit
longer, uh has been generally the flow
has been towards like more egalitarian,
more progressive. Um and so the math
people have gotten an an advantage. Um
but yeah, may maybe that could be
reversing.
>> Yeah. So, we were speaking with Chris
Camilillo yesterday who's telling us
that he wants his kids to be just
welltraveled, interesting people who are
good with networking because in a world
with AI, he thinks that in-person
relationships and conversations are
going to matter more than they ever
have. And if a person is really
wellraveled, who has interesting stories
and knows how to relate to someone else,
that'll be irreplaceable by any sort of
program.
>> I think my point of view is is a little
bit different. I still think math is
very very important
because my experience is math
generalizes. So if you're really really
good at solving
theoretical math problems and I don't
mean just like multiplying together big
numbers. I mean like abstract
theoretical math. It it's a pure form of
problem solving. And that pure form of
problem solving can generalize to all
kinds of business situations. I mean, I
studied math. I was pretty good at it. I
never studied business. Um, but I felt
like being better at math trained me to
think better and thinking better helps
you in in business and so many other
things. Um,
so I I do think it's helpful and I think
that um, you know, be being better at
thinking and thinking clearly helps you
as you're networking or creating
relationships as well. The the things
needed to be better at math help you
become more curious. So I I I view it as
very fundamental. Yeah. which is in part
why I also started another company a
couple years ago building AI for math uh
what I call mathematical super
intelligence and and the bet there is if
you become if you build a system that's
really really good at math it can
basically be really good at any economic
activity starting with coding which is
the closest but probably it can write
you a better history essay uh eventually
as well. How has your perspective
changed over the last nine months since
we last filmed?
>> Well, I've shipped social as per your
recommendation.
>> You're very welcome.
>> You asked me before what products are
people not talking about enough. I still
think even though there is a policy
discussion on private markets.
Uh we have to do more to like spread the
word that hey this asset class is now
available to individual investors. And I
think we've we've been trying to do that
through various means, but it's not like
um I don't think we're we're at the
point where it's had its full mass
market moment. So these are kind of
undiscovered little gems that only
relatively few customers know about.
Agentic Trading, another example.
There's a lot of policy discussion on
it. The folks that are extremely
sophisticated are aware of it, but it's
still 100,000. It's not at
>> 10 million customers. So there there's a
lot of growing there. Yeah. And I think
now, you know, me personally,
I mean, probably the first time we
spoke, Graham, was 2021, right? That was
what, uh, 5 years ago?
>> Yeah, I think so. Yeah,
>> 5 years ago. Um, I think I've gone
through from this journey of being kind
of a newbie
uh, young person in this industry to now
kind of being in the middle, right?
Still young enough to kind of understand
what the Gen Z's are doing and saying,
even though I really can't figure out
Tik Tok yet. Haven't made much progress
there. But now I'm kind of old enough to
um
I guess be be thought of as an industry
person. And I think this middle area is
kind of interesting for me, right?
because I can kind of hang in
Washington, have a policy discussion,
and be taken seriously, maybe in a way
that 25 or 30-year-old Vlad wouldn't
have, but I can I'm still kind of um in
touch with, you know, all all of the all
the folks on social media, all the folks
in the trenches, and um the ability to
kind of bridge both um I think is is
unique given where I am in life. and and
uh I'm just I'm just trying to enjoy
that and take advantage of it.
>> Yeah, I do have to say you're doing an
incredible job. And I think the last
time that Jack and I were here, we both
left thinking that oh my gosh, your
passion like the fact that you would
come on a podcast and talk with us
openly for two hours and nothing was off
limits and you just allowed like that I
think speaks volumes and after that I'm
like oh man I am bullish on Robin Hood.
I really, but it's I think it's because
of you [clears throat] specifically,
>> not necessarily Robin Hood as a company,
but because of your passion and your
enthusiasm and how into it you are.
>> So, I think that goes like a long long
way. I think the the exciting thing
about Robin Hood is I I become more uh
bullish and excited um as the years pass
because the mission itself becomes much
more expansive and much more interesting
and now we're talking about things that
are on a civilizational scale like how
can we increase the ability of billions
of people to own stocks, own private
companies, own real world assets. Um,
and I think that's a really, really hard
problem. And to actually move the needle
on that, you need to do lots of other
little things, right, that are very hard
to do. And you have to engage and
entertain people because inherently
these are kind of boring things. And
you're never going to get everyone
unless you make it make it a little bit
more engaging as well.
>> If you were consulting our podcast, our
business, what do you think we could be
doing better? So, a little reverse
interview.
>> Um, let's see. How many viewers are you
guys at now?
>> Total subscribers, uh, 1.63 million on
YouTube, but it's way more
>> across all platforms, millions.
>> How many viewers per episode? Probably
on average. And there is some volatility
there, but like on average maybe 300 to
400,000 people listen to every episode.
>> That's the long form. And that's the
long form, but then on top of that, we
have distribution. So, we have like
clips and we have shorts and we're on
every social media platform. Last year,
we did 1.2 uh 1.2 billion views um
across all platforms.
>> Okay. And and what is your north star?
Like if you wanted to be remembered for
one thing, one contribution for the
podcast, what what would that be?
>> That's really the guest selection. We
just want to have really inspiring
guests who could teach our audience
something and show them a different
perspective that maybe they didn't
consider before. And so for me, it's
just getting the best guest possible who
we just want to have a conversation
with.
>> Got it. But is it like
we want to get to a 100 million
subscribers, does that matter? Getting
to a billion subscriber, getting a
billion views per podcast. Is that is
that like an anti- goal or
>> No, I think like at this point in terms
of growth like I think growth is sort of
something that will ensue to our other
goal which is like talk to interesting
people you know be as objective as
possible and fair and be entertaining
and fun and funny but also you know
educational.
>> If you had to think and you don't have
to say me obviously I know that it's me
but besides me who what was the best
episode that you
>> you have had? It's hard to say best
because we've been doing this six years,
so we're picking between hundreds of
people. But like most memorable eps
would be Dr. K, who's like a
psychiatrist, oddly enough, who's been
trained in eastern and western medicine.
>> Um, and that was fascinating. Also,
another one we love talking to Ben Ma,
like the commercial real estate, Kevin,
Chris Camilillo, Strad man, who's like a
car, like we just have so many everybody
that virtually every person we talk to,
we're like super super super excited.
>> Like to have them back on. Papa John,
you know, that was absurd to be able to
talk to him at his house.
>> And string theory. He's really into
string theory. Papa John likes string
theory.
>> Yeah. He brought it up unprompted.
>> Wow.
>> Yeah. We had no idea what to do, but it
was it was fun.
>> Yeah. String theory is uh
>> Please don't. [laughter]
>> Where we're getting at is that we feel
like we have so much potential and we
have such a big impactful platform that
we just don't know what's next. and
we're good at this,
>> but we feel like there's something more.
There's something extra that we could be
doing, and we don't know what on earth
it is.
>> Also, to be frank, I think we're
severely undermonetized. Like,
realistically, to be able to get 1.2
billion views and
>> in the finance space,
>> in the finance space, like I I
>> I don't think that we're like I just
want to focus on this. I don't really
want to focus on like a business or
something to like redirect viewership to
or more sales. I want to focus just on
content. But also in I think that a lot
of other people if given the uh the
maximal amount of marketing that we're
able to like provide basically for free
>> um they would be able to turn a greater
profit.
>> Yeah, I think that makes sense. Um,
yeah, I guess. And and if you think
about these shows, the the the best
where you felt that you've done the best
work.
>> Is it do you judge it based on views or
comments or how the audience has
resonated with it or is it more like,
hey, that was a really good conversation
for me. I loved being a part of that. I
felt
>> it's got to be both. Yeah, it's got to
be both. Because I look at the metrics
and I'm very analytical about the data
and I say, "Ah, this underperformed.
why? And then I try to improve it
because if it underperforms, I think
that means the audience didn't watch
enough of it and they clicked out. Why
did they click out? Why did they not
like that? But for me personally, I also
just enjoy the conversations.
>> Yeah. I mean, I think that I can tell
it's a labor of love for you guys that
you really care about it. You're trying
to get better. It's really engaging. Um
Yeah. And I think that uh it it comes
across. I mean, I I enjoy watching it.
Um, I think that if I had to give one
uh area for improvement,
I think that the the sort of like north
star of having really interesting guests
that you guys want to learn from and you
think the audience could learn from is
is probably one that you'd hear from a
lot of podcasts. like basically lots of
podcasts just want to have fun guests
and uh have it be great educational
content. But um I guess the the answer
to the question of
you know why would I watch you know
Graham and Jack versus those others
could use more differentiation right um
like what is the one thing that they'll
get here that they won't get anywhere
I'll give you an example I listen to
acquired podcast and I just don't think
anyone else does exactly what they do
you So if if I if if I get uh another
episode of that, I know exactly what it
is. It's like a 4hour thing where those
guys are having fun and chatting, but
it's like a 4-hour deep dive on one
specific company. I kind of know the
formula. Um
>> and and I think it's differentiated in a
sense. Um, yeah. And in your your guys,
it's a little bit of finance, a little
bit of pop culture, but I think a a
sharper differentiation might might be
something I would consider.
>> We always try to tie everything into
finance a little bit with some guests.
Obviously, it's sort of impossible and
we're just excited to talk to them. But
we always do generally dial it back into
some form of like where are you
investing? Yes. you know, do you own
equities or you
>> or the philosophies on business? Like
everyone we've had on is successful in
their own right in their thing and what
could we take away from that.
>> Yeah.
>> But it is still, you know, relatively
vague. Yes. Like I couldn't tell you a
specific claim like, oh well, we want to
get as many people into like retail
investing as possible.
>> I think that the the finance aspect is a
interesting direction. And I remember
the the clips that I've seen of your
guys's that really resonate are where
you talk finances with a successful
person that [clears throat]
actually you wouldn't normally associate
with with finance like that. Uh who who
was it?
>> Kiicular.
>> That was our goal years ago was like we
want to break into the mainstream and
make like talking about finance a more
available ubiquitous thing. Like we
wanted to have Leonard Leonard on the
like this was a couple years ago like
bring on people that are celebrities,
musicians, yada yada yada. Hey, how much
do you make selling out Madison Square
Garden?
>> Like who actually gets paid out from
this? Like what are you doing with this
money? Like what are your intentions
with it? Like that's what we wanted. But
it's also very difficult because like we
we try that like we'll bring you on the
show and then we'll heavily debate
beforehand, hey, should we lead in with
a question or a phrase saying something
like, oh, Robin Hood moved 3% today,
meaning your personal wealth grew by
this amount. Like that that is directing
our audience towards that that north
star. But at the same time, it could put
you on your heels a little bit. It could
make it seem like we're out to get you
or like we're just another one of those
podcasts that want to pocket cheap.
>> Yeah. No. Yeah. I think you guys do it
um uh yeah in kind of a a nice way. Um
yeah, I never felt like it was um like
uh out to get me or or aggressive. I
think that there is a delicate balance,
right? if you want to get into
deep questions that are just
you not what you would hear at at other
podcasts, but you know, a a lot of
executives are probably
trained to some degree to not answer
deep questions. Um, and sometimes we
also forget, right? We're also like,
well,
>> shoot, I have to say a number. If I say
the wrong number, you know, we'd have to
edit that out or issue a correction. So
there can be an incentive to not really
remember numbers, right?
>> Yeah.
>> Um but yeah. Yeah. And and I think um
what I've seen other people do that's
kind of interesting is real time just
like start browsing the web or show
something or you know, hey, I found this
funny tweet, pop that up um almost as
like a visual source. And I think I
think that can make it a little bit more
dynamic, interactive, entertaining. So,
here's another thing, and this is by no
means a pitch, but I think that so many
companies could benefit so much from
having an unlimited marketing funnel
behind them of like organic marketing,
like not paid, not just like a
sponsorship, not running an ad because
that appears as an ad. it appears as a
sponsor. But like if the full power of
the iced coffee hour was put behind some
sort of fintech company or like some
sort of you know huge like finance
newsletter or business or platform or
something like that where consistently
you have you know 1 billion views every
year that's also growing and you have
the the trust and the faith of the brand
behind a company. it would be worth 20
times what we're making on an annual
basis. Like, and it's not even close.
You don't see companies like actually
try to create legitimate podcasts. Like,
for example, we talked to John Morgan
about it and he spent $2 billion on
advertising this year
>> and we were like, "Yeah, but what about
like like organic social media reach
where there's more trust behind it?"
>> Like, why are companies not doing that?
The overhead is it's it's cheap relative
to everything else. And it's also an
added added Yeah, it's an issue. It's an
added element of like like trust and
authenticity.
>> Yeah, I think that's right. And you
know, we've we've dipped our toes in uh
media as a company for a while. We
acquired Market Snacks if you guys
remember. That was something like 8
years ago became Robin Hood Snacks and
there was a podcast. Robin Hood Snacks
was a podcast with uh Nick and Jack and
they later went off to with our support
launch another thing TBOY right so they
have a podcast now um I don't think it's
as big as the iced coffee hour but uh
they've been they've been working on it
we had Sherwood Media as well I think
that's evolved over time and I think
that we uh we see huge potential in
connecting our customers with really
good content. Um, and I I don't think
too many people have nailed it. I think
Bloomberg has done a a pretty good job
of like combining financial services and
data with with content, media, and
distribution, but they've kind of been
unique. And, you know, our our thought
is always how much of it is curated
versus providing a platform for the best
content from all over the world to to
live on Robin Hood. And and I think I
see more potential in the latter because
there's just it's probably unrealistic
for
the best content to be created first
party. So instead, what we should figure
out is how to just empower folks such as
yourselves who are basically
entrepreneurs, probably don't want to
work for a big company, but want to
create great content and monetize it.
How can we actually be a conduit for
that great content? no matter where it's
made to find its way to Robin Hood users
as cheaply as possible. Um, I think
that's that's that's going to be the
winning long-term strategy because we
want customers to get the best content.
We're unlikely to be able to employ
everyone that can make it. And so, uh,
and then we also probably to get really
good external content don't want them to
feel like we're prioritizing the
editorial stuff. It sounds very similar
to like Elon Musk's approach of like I'm
not going to buy ads from anybody. I'm
just going to make the product so loud
that you can't ignore it effectively
like that. Like people will inevitably
talk about any sort of Tesla launch
>> because it's just such like a
groundbreaking thing.
>> Yeah, I think that it's simpler in many
ways because you get to be a neutral
platform. Uh you can just work on
building the best tools possible. Um and
then you know I think uh it's simple to
understand for creators on the platform
as well. Whenever we're building network
products which we have at least two new
ones since the last time we spoke Robin
Hood chain and Robin Hood social we end
up you know we're thinking about how to
make it
>> as as really attractive as possible for
a creator or a developer to to be on the
platform. And it's really just giving
them the best tools, making them
understand that the goal is for it to be
neutral and for it to be a meritocracy
and there's no like hidden agenda or
hidden favoritism that can tip the
scales one way or another and get you
demonetized uh without you understanding
why. So it's still super early. I mean
both of these things are like month one.
But um yeah, we are spending more time
thinking through
>> these problems. Rapid fire questions.
What do you have to say about the
biggest investing myth?
>> I think what people don't understand is
compound interest. And a lot of people
say don't start investing until you have
money saved up and you you know what
you're doing. And actually, I think it's
the opposite. The earlier you start, the
better off you'll be. So, with Trump
accounts, you could start at age zero.
So, we've we've taken it to uh its
logical conclusion, which is I think the
the right place. Investing at age zero.
Yeah.
>> Are you the largest depositor on Robin
Hood app?
>> No.
>> Who outside of yourself is the best
product builder?
>> I think Spotify has done a really really
nice job. Yeah, I I uh I I think Spotify
is a great product. Uh I'm sure you guys
would agree, but it's just
>> they're great.
>> I love using it. Yeah. What does Robin
Hood look like in 10 years if everything
goes perfectly?
>> I think that um Robin Hood should be
helping you with every
every investment, everything that you
own, whether it be digital through our
smartphone or physical. Maybe you'll be
using our Robin Hood credit card at a
Robin Hood grocery store.
>> Driving a Robin Hood car.
>> Driving a Robin Hood car. Maybe maybe
you'll be checking time on your Robin
Hood watch and uh
>> a Robin Hood plane. Yes. And you'll get
free burgers at our fast food
restaurants.
>> Robin Hood Wellness Centers, free cold
plunge. And so
>> I like that. What will surprise
everybody by 2035?
>> You know, one of the things that uh I'm
really pushing is private markets. And I
think the degree to which we can
democratize that and make that
accessible will be uh will be surprising
to people. I mean, two hot takes. I
think there will be more software
engineers and more lawyers in 2035 than
today.
>> Okay. Well, that's that's just dangling
the carrot, huh? [laughter] That's just
>> All right. Well, you guys heard it here.
We'll explore more of that next episode.
Thank you so much for watching this
episode. Thank you to Vlad for coming on
the podcast. It's always a pleasure to
talk to you.
>> Thank you guys.
>> Really appreciate it. Until next time.
>> Till next time.
>> There's nothing to stop the [music]
music like the word billionaire.
>> Do you have a billion in the bank?
>> I'm a billionaire.
A real one. What was your business? I
own one of the largest law firms in
North America. I hunt money. I fish for
money.
>> Income and wealth disparity in the US
are at all-time high levels.
>> Nobody wants to say, "Look, here's the
real reason I'm a lazy slug."
>> What do most people get wrong [music]
about your business?
>> I am the most authentic person you're
ever going to meet. But I'm very very
street smart and my social [music] IQ is
off the charts.
>> So how did you become a liquid net worth
billionaire?
>> If [music] work is work, you're I love
to work cuz I don't lose.
They lose. And when somebody with me, I
back
[music]